接待员∶迈克西维尔!
Receptionist: Mike Seaver!
迈克∶给你我的号码.
Mike: Here's my number then.
试镜员∶你好,迈克.
Auditioner: Hello, Mike.
迈克∶你好,很高兴见到你.
Mike: Oh, hi, very nice to meet you.
试镜员∶那是道具书吗?
Auditioner: Are those prop books?
迈克∶不是.我是阿尔福蓝登学院的学生.事实上,
Mike: Err...oh, oh, no.See, I go to Alf Landen Junior College.
此时此刻,我应该呆在教室里上课,当我看到你们在进行电视节目的试镜时,
In fact that's where I'm supposed to be right now,
but when I read about this open audition for a TV show, I cut class
哦,我的话太多了,对吗?
Oh, and you got Morgan Chase...wow.I should shut up, right?
试镜员∶迈克,一般情况下,我只在几十个人演员里挑八个.
Auditioner: Mike, I usually get eight by tens for my actors.
迈克∶哦,哦,
Mike: Oh, oh, well...ah...
我只是刚刚开始,所以我有三分之二的机遇.
see I'm just starting out, so I'm using two by threes.
但是,我会努力的.
But I'm gonna work my way up.
试镜员∶你都有什么表演经历?
Auditioner: What kind of experience do you have?
迈克∶呃,
Mike: Ah, well...errm...
我参加过在林肯中心举行的一次戏剧试镜,
I auditioned for a play at the Lincoln Centre,
还有小黑鱼电视广告的试镜,
and I auditioned for the Swimmy the happy fish commercial,
并且差点做了滚筒式除臭剂.
and I was this close to being a roll-on deodorant.
试镜员∶星期四要进行拍摄,你有时间吗?
Auditioner: Now, this shoot's next Thursday, will you be available?
迈克∶我得到了这个角色!我得到了这个角色!
Mike: I got the part!I got the part!
试镜员∶不,迈克,
Auditioner: No, Mike, Mike, I'm just checking you're availability.
迈克,我只是问你有没有时间.你学校那天有课吗?
Do you have school that day?
迈克∶我会逃课!
Mike: I'll drop out!
试镜员∶好吧,让我们试试……你读布考斯基军官的台词,
Auditioner: OK.Let's give this a try...err...
我读莎拉军官的台词.现在,
you're reading for Officer Bukowski, I'll read Officer Sarah's lines.
我们正在拍你,你可以站起来.布考斯基,
Now, you've just been shot.You can stand.
对不起,那子弹是要打我的;你为什么要这么做呢?
Bukowski, I'm sorry, that bullet was meant for me; why'd you do it?
迈克∶啊……莎拉,我发生什么事都无所谓,
Mike: Ah...it doesn't matter what happens to me Sarah,
可是你有爱你的家人……
but you've got a family who loves you...
试镜员∶挺住,救护车马上就来了.
Auditioner: Hang on, there's an ambulance on the way.
迈克∶莎拉,我不可能当上中士了,对吗?
Mike: Sarah, I'm not gonna make Sergeant, am I?
试镜员∶谢谢.
Auditioner: Thank you.
迈克∶不用谢.
Mike: You're welcome.
试镜员∶不,你现在可以走了.
Auditioner: No, see, you're supposed to say goodbye, now.
迈克∶哦!哦!再见.
Mike: Oh, oh, right.Goodbye.
试镜员∶哈.他让我想起了年轻时候的迈克尔J.福克斯.
Auditioner: Ha.He reminds me of a young Michael J.Fox.
本∶你说的是真的?真的吗?太好了!
Ben: You mean it?Really?Yes!Alright!
开萝尔∶本,什么好消息?
Carol: Good news, Ben?
本∶是我人生中最好的消息!我是义卖会的一员了!
Ben: The best of my life!I'm in the bake sale!
杰森∶本,也许我给了你复合信号.
Jason: Maybe I've been sending you mixed signals, Ben.
你真要去参加吗?连足球都不看了?
You want to go and toss the old football around?
本∶不,爸爸,你知道吗?
Ben: No, Dad.See, the lovely Laura-Lynn's running the bake sale.
义卖会是可爱的劳拉林发起的.她怎么会忍心看着一个小伙子手里300片巧克力碎片饼干熔化呢.哦,
I mean, how can she ignore a dude with three hundred chocolate-chip cookies,
对了,妈妈,我明天就要.
melting in his hands.Oh, by the way Mom, I'll need those by tomorrow.
麦琪∶等等,本.
Maggie: Hold on, Ben.
你只跟我说需要300片饼干,然后就离开吗?
You think, you can just tell me to make three hundred cookies, and leave.
本∶妈妈,你最伟大.
Ben: Mom, you're the greatest.
迈克∶妈妈!爸爸!
Mike: Mom!Dad!The coolest thing happened today!
今天发生了最酷的事情!你们永远都猜不到发生了什么!试着猜猜看!
You're never gonna guess what happened!Go on, take a guess!
不,你们一定猜不到!
No, you'll never guess!
开萝尔∶你也参加了义卖.
Carol: You're in the bake sale, too.
迈克∶不,不,
Mike: No.No, look, a bunch of us guys from acting class,
我们一大帮表演班的人去参加开放试镜,你们准备好了吗?
we all went to this open audition, and...are you ready for this?
我要...真是太酷了,你们肯定不会相信...
I am going to be...oh this is so cool, you can't even believe it...
我被选中参演ABC电台的系列剧,纽约风暴!
on ABC's hit series, New York Heat!
杰森:不.
Jason: No.
麦琪∶你要上电视了!
Maggie: You got a part on television!
迈克∶没错!出演纽约风暴!制片人是亚伦斯泊林先生.
Mike: Yeah!On New York Heat!Produced...produced by Mr.Aaron Spelling.
杰森∶主角是摩尔根奇斯!
Jason: Starring Morgan Chase!
迈克∶没错.
Mike: Yeah.
杰森∶你要见到她了!
Jason: You're gonna meet her!
杰森∶对!
Mike: Yeah!
杰森∶喔喔,她是个有天赋的演员.
Jason: Woo woo!She's a...She's very talented.
迈克∶是的,爸爸.
Mike: Yeah Dad, and I play Officer Bukowski, the heroic rookie cop,
我演布考斯基军官,英勇的新兵警官,在执勤的时候因为中枪而牺牲!
who takes a bullet and dies in the line of duty!
杰森∶你要牺牲?
Jason: You die!
杰森∶对!
Mike: Yeah
麦琪∶哦!太好了!
Maggie: Oh, that's wonderful!!
开萝尔∶他们为什么不选专业演员,而选你呢?
Carol: Well, why did they pick you, over a real actor?
迈克∶专业演员?开萝尔,
Mike: A real actor?Ah.
我知道这么多年以来,我们一直都互相取笑,
You know, I know we teased each other a lot over the years, Carol, but...
但是……这次我希望你能理解,
I...I thought that maybe this time you'd understand;
这是我的重大突破.可能一生中就这么 次,
I mean this is my big break.
所以,你应该为我高兴才对.
I thought that just for maybe once, you'd be happy for me.
开萝尔∶我只是开玩笑而已.我们不是经常互相开玩笑吗?
Carol: I was only kidding.I mean, that's just what Mike and I do.
杰森∶恩,开萝尔,也许你这次有点过分了.
Jason: Yeah, well maybe this time you've gone a little too far, Carol.
开萝尔∶我去道歉.
Carol: I'll go and apologise.
迈克∶不是真正的演员,深呼吸.
Mike: Not a real actor, rat breath.
迈克∶不,不,
Mike: No, no, no, Operah, my first role was not opposite De Niro in Street;
不,欧波拉,我的第一个角色不是在街上的反面角色德尼若;而是在纽约风暴里.
it was on New York Heat.You know what, Operah, we have something in common...
你知道吗?欧波拉,我们俩有很多共同点……你听我说,
I'll tell you, I'll tell you...
你听我说,在收视指南封面上的我用的是安妮玛格丽特的替身.
When I was on the cover of TV guide, they used Anne Margaret's body too.
本∶嗨!迈克.
Ben: Hey, Mike...
迈克∶哦!嗨!嗨!本!你听说那个好消息了吗?
Mike: Oh, hey, hey, hey Benny!Did you hear the great news?
本∶是,你要演纽约风暴了.
Ben: Yeah; you're gonna be on New York Heat.
迈克∶没多!是爸妈告诉你的吗?
Mike: Right!Did Mom and Dad tell you?
本∶不是的,我听开萝尔在电话里说的.
Ben: No, I heard Carol talking on the phone.
她一直在电话里对她的朋友们吹嘘你呢.
She'd been calling all her friends and bragging about you.
迈克∶开萝尔会这样做吗?
Mike: This is our sister you're talking about?
本∶是的.就是整天一副臭脸的开萝尔.
Ben: Yeah, the one with the constipated look.
迈克∶呵呵,真有意思.
Mike: Well, well, well.This is very interesting.
本∶我早就知道你一定会上电视的,但是,
Ben: You know, I always knew you'd end up on TV.
我一直认为会出现在新闻里.
But, I figured it would be on the News.
迈克∶嗨!既然你在这里,要不要帮我练练台词?
Mike: Hey, as long as you're here, you wanna help me run my lines?
本∶我?
Ben: Me?
迈克∶就是你!你现在演莎拉麦考利军官.
Mike: Yeah, yeah, look.OK, now you can play, Officer Sarah McCauley.
本∶你是说摩尔根奇斯?
Ben: You mean, Morgan Chase?
迈克∶没错.
Mike: Yeah.
本∶乎乎乎!
Ben: Ho ho ho!
迈克:好的.你在做什么?
Mike: Yeah, OK, alright.Now, I've just been shot, OK?What are you doing?
本∶我在酝酿感情.
Ben: I'm getting into character.
迈克∶好了.嘣!啊……
Mike: OK.Bang!Ah...ah.
本∶哦!布考斯基,那子弹本来是朝我来的,你为什么要这么做?
Ben: Oh, Bukowski, that bullet was meant for me; why'd you do it?
迈克∶啊……莎拉,我发生什么事都无所谓,
Mike: Oh...it doesn't matter what happens to me, Sarah,
可是你有爱你的家人……
but you've got a family who loves you.
本∶挺住,救护车马上就来了.
Ben: Hang on, there's an ambulance on the way.
迈克∶莎拉,我不可能当上中士了,对吗?
Mike: Sarah, I'm not gonna make Sergeant, am I?
本∶我每天都会见到死亡,但是我还是不能习惯.
Ben: I see this every day, and I never get used to it.
杰森∶本,家庭作业,如果没有家庭作业的话,我们去附近踢踢球.
Jason: Ben, homework, or no homework, we're tossing the football around.
本∶爸爸,你看,我们刚刚正在……
Ben: Dad, see, we were just err...
杰森∶下去吧!我要和迈克谈谈……本,
Jason: Go on!I've gotta talk to Mike...
不要让你妈妈看见你拿着那些胸脯画.迈克……
and Ben, don't let your mother see you with those breasts.Mike...
迈克∶爸爸,爸爸,
Mike: Dad, Dad, look, I was doing my homework, alright?
你看,我正在做我的家庭作业呢?所以呢,
So, look, you don't have to worry, this...
你根本就不用担心,演出会影响我的学习.
this part is not gonna interfere with my homework at all.
杰森∶忘记学校!
Jason: Forget school!
迈克∶哼!?
Mike: Huh?
杰森∶你能不能帮我搞一张摩尔根奇斯的亲笔签名?
Jason: Could you get me Morgan Chase's autograph?
导演∶替身!!准备好了吗?
Director: Stand-in!!You ready?
迈克∶准备好了.
Mike: Ready.
导演∶把他们卷起来!痛打它!预备,标志!
Director: Roll 'em!Slate it!In one-twelve, take one!Marker!And...action!
开始!等信号……开枪!开枪!关掉!!开始!
Wait for the cue...Gunshot!!Gunshot!!Switch!!And...action!
演员∶布考斯基被打中了!
Actor: Bukowski's been hit!
摩尔根奇斯∶布考斯基,对不起!
Morgan Chase: Bukowski, I'm sorry!That bullet was meant for me!
那子弹摩尔根追来是朝我来的,你为什么要这么做?
Why'd you do it?
迈克∶莎拉,我发生什么事都无所谓,
Mike: Sarah, it doesn't matter what happens to me,
可是你有爱你的家人...
but you have a family who loves you.
摩尔根奇斯∶挺住救护车马上就来了.
Morgan Chase: Hang on!There's an ambulance on the way.
迈克∶莎拉.
Mike: Sarah.
摩尔根奇斯∶是.
Morgan Chase: Yeah.
迈克∶莎拉,我不可能当上中士了,对吗?
Mike: I'm not gonna make Sergeant, am I?
摩尔根奇斯:你还是个孩子.我每天都在经历这些,
Morgan Chase: You're just a kid.
但是还是不能承受.
I see this every day, and I never get used to it.
导演∶停!!!很好.我们完成了.
Director: And cut!!!Was it good for you.OK, we got it.Let's move into closure.
我们封机吧.孩子,你做的很不错.
Nice job, kid!
迈克∶谢谢,理查德!嗨!保罗,
Mike: Thank you, Richard.Hey, I owe you, Paul.Gracias, PJ.Dude!
我欠你的.格雷西斯,PJ.伙计!他跟我说,
He said, nice job!!You wanna congratulate me?
干的好!!你们要祝贺我吗?他特意挪出时间亲自来叫我:孩子,啊哈!
He took the time to personally, call me, kid.Aha!
摩尔根奇斯∶迈克,劳驾.
Morgan Chase: Excuse me, Mike.
迈克∶哇,她知道我的名字.
Mike: Wow, she knows me, by name.
麦琪∶本,跟你准备好了饼干.花了我一整天,
Maggie: Ben, I made your cookies.
不过呢,作为无私的母亲,我觉得很开心.
Took me all day, but that's the joy of being the selfless mother, I am.
本∶妈妈,忘记告诉你;我退出义卖会了.
Ben: Mom, I forgot to tell you; I dropped out of the bake sale.
麦琪∶什么?
Maggie: What?
本∶当我告诉劳拉林,迈克要上电视后,
Ben: Well, see, when I told Laura-Lynn that Mike was gonna be on TV,
她兴奋的不得了,谁还要饼干呢?
she got all excited, so who needs cookies?
杰森∶你要我帮你抓着他吗?以便你能好好的修理他?
Jason: Want me to hold him, while you smack him around?
麦琪∶你给我坐下,就在这里,
Maggie: I want you to sit down, right here young man, and eat these cookies...
吃完300块饼干.
all three hundred of them.
本∶好吧!!
Ben: Alright!!
迈克∶他们喜欢我,他们真的喜欢我!!
Mike: They liked me...they really liked me!!
杰森∶嘿!
Jason: Hey!
迈克∶爸爸,你好.导演亲自跟我说,干的好!
Mike: Yeah!Yeah Dad, and the Director himself said, nice job!
杰森∶太棒了,迈克.
Jason: Well that's great, Mike.
麦琪∶太棒了,宝贝!
Maggie: That's great, honey!
迈克∶看,这是我的合同!上面写着,
Mike: Yeah, yeah, here's my contract, look!
迈克尔西维尔,此处和以下简称艺术家.我现在是艺术家了.
It says, Michael Seaver, here and after the artist.I am now legally an artist.
本∶我也要.
Ben: I'll get it.
杰森∶我们儿子的第一份合同.迈克,我们要把它裱糊起来!
Jason: Alright, our son's first contract.We're gonna get this framed, Mike!
本∶迈克,表演班的托尼找你.
Ben: Mike, it's Tony from the acting class.
迈克:好.我们要研究一下,告诉他我会给他回电话.
Mike: Oh, oh, right.We gotta study tonight...errm...Tell him I'll call him back later.
本∶他会回电话给你.
Ben: He'll call you back later.
杰森∶我很高兴,你还跟得上你的学业.
Jason: And I'm glad to hear, you're keeping up with your school work too.
迈克∶哦!那当然.爸爸,这是你的摩尔根奇斯的亲笔签名.
Mike: Oh yeah, and Dad here's your autographed picture of Morgan Chase.
杰森∶哦!你怎么知道我想要一张?
Jason: Oh!!Where'd you get the idea, I'd want one of those?
迈克∶爸爸,是你告诉我的.
Mike: From you, Dad.
杰森∶开萝尔,你弟弟今天在纽约风暴的表演棒级了.
Jason: Carol, your brother knocked 'em dead today on New York Heat.
开萝尔∶只不过是愚蠢的电视节目罢了.
Carol: It's just a stupid TV show.
迈克∶开萝尔,你这样说我很伤心,我真的很伤心.
Mike: That hurts, Carol.You know, that really, really hurts.
麦琪:开萝尔.
Maggie: Carol!
开萝尔∶妈妈,他又在演戏了.他真的是个不错的演员.
Carol: Mom, he was just acting again.He's a good actor.
杰森∶去跟他道歉.
Jason: Well go tell him that.
麦琪∶她不得不打击一下他,这是人之常情.
Maggie: She had to have this re-touched, nobody is this gorgeous.
杰森∶哦!某人也是.
Jason: Oh...somebody is.
麦琪∶太小了,太迟了.
Maggie: Too little, too late.
迈克∶(打电话)我没有发疯,托尼.我有理由不去参加测试.你知道我的演绎生涯刚刚起步,我不需要学习了,我打算退学.对,托尼,我是认真的.我可不想你把这件事情告诉其他人,行不?先替我保守秘密.开萝尔!托尼,我晚点再和你聊,好吗?当然,我不会退学,托尼,我开玩笑而已!好了,再见,(放下电话).哦!表演真是太简单了.
Mike:(on the phone) I am not crazy, Tony.I have a reason for not studying for this test tomorrow.Look, with my acting career taking off, I don't need to study, I'm dropping out of school.Yeah, Tony, I'm serious.Look, I don't want you telling any one yet, alright?So just put a sock in your big...Carol!Look, Tony, I'll talk to you later, OK?Of course, I'm not dropping out of school, Tony, I was just kidding!Yeah, alright.Later.(puts the phone down) Oh, man, this acting stuff is almost too easy.
开萝尔∶你不是在演戏!你难道就因为一次低廉的电视节目表演工作而决定放弃学业吗?
Carol: You weren't acting!
You're really gonna quit school over one crummy acting job on one stupid
TV show!
迈克:你说ABC电台的电视节目很愚蠢?
M ike: You're calling a TV show on ABC, stupid!
开萝尔∶是的,如果你要退学的话!
Carol: Yes, if it means you're gonna quit!
迈克,你要仔细考虑清楚.
Mike, think, or get as close to it as you can.
我是说,如果这份工作只是侥幸呢?
I mean, what if this job was a fluke?
如果你以后都不再工作了呢?如果,
I mean, what if you never work again?
这件事情是开始也是结束恩?你会痛苦,
What if, this is the beginning of the end?
落寞而悲惨的结束,到时就只有家庭才是你唯一的安慰!
A painful, lonely, bitter end, with your family as your only solace!
迈克∶如果我把你冲下马桶会怎么样?
Mike: What if I flush you down my toilet?
开萝尔∶我会看你的将来!
Carol: I'd see your future there!
迈克∶开萝尔,当本跟我说你在电话里跟你所有的朋友吹嘘我时,我就应该意识到,那是本在骗我!!
Mike: Oh, oh, you know Carol, I should have known that Ben was crazy when he told me that you were bragging to all you friends about me!!
开萝尔∶什么?
Carol: What?
迈克∶长这么大,你从来都没有相信过我一次.
Mike: You have never, ever, in your entire life, believed in me.
你现在怎么能了解呢?我现在只希望你闭上你的嘴巴,
So how could you possibly understand this now?
在我没上电视前,别跟爸妈提我要退学的事情!
What I want you to do,
行吗?你能做到吗?
is just keep your mouth shut until I tell Mom and Dad the news,
哼!哼!
after they see me on TV!OK, can you do that, huh, huh?
开萝尔∶知道了.
Carol: Yes.
迈克∶好.
Mike: Good.
开萝尔∶迈克,不管你是否明白,我是爱你的,我也会支持你,一直支持你.
Carol: Mike, whether you know it or not, I love you, I support you, I'm on your side.
迈克∶我不知道说什么.
Mike: Well, I don't know what to say.
开萝尔∶每个人都可以演戏!加油!
Carol: See, anybody can act!Bozo!
本∶还有5分钟就到纽约风暴了.
Ben: Five minutes to New York Heat.
麦琪∶是的,妈妈,他演Bukowski,
Maggie: That's right, Mom, he plays Bukowski,
英勇的新兵,在执勤的时候由于中弹而牺牲.哦,
the heroic rookie who takes a bullet and dies in the line of duty.
Oh, and you'll call Mark and Stacey for me?Great, thanks
杰森∶在长岛上,还有谁不知道迈克今晚要上电视了?
Jason: Is there anyone on Long Island who doesn't know that Mike's on TV tonight?
麦琪∶没有了.
Maggie: Yes.
迈克∶在不到5分钟内,
Mike: In less than five minutes,
全国的制作人和经纪公司都会见到我了,
I will be seen by Producers and agents all across the country and they
他们肯定会把我们家的门槛都踏破……吼吼……他们提前来了!
will be beating a path to my door.Wo ho, they're early!
本∶不是的,迈克,是我可爱的女朋友.臭虫,你来干什么?
Ben: No Mike, this is my lovely date.Stinky, what are you doing here?
臭虫∶嗨!迈克,很感谢你请我来看你的首次演出.
Stinky: Hey Mike, thanks for having me at your debut.
迈克∶哦!嗨!真的……
Mike: Oh sure, hey it's real...
本∶要开始了!
Ben: It's about time!
劳拉∶什么?
Laura-Lynn: What?
本∶节目马上就要开始了,你总是很准时,亲爱的.
Ben: For the show to start.But you're as punctual as always, dear.
劳拉∶准时好.
Laura-Lynn: That's better.
本∶我相信你记得我的哥哥.
Ben: I'm sure you remember my brother.
劳拉∶见到大明星,总是让人觉得特别兴奋.
Laura-Lynn: It's always enchanting to meet someone who's tasted celebrity.
臭虫,去帮我把东西拿来.你能帮我签名吗?
Stinky...fetch.May I have your autograph?
迈克∶哦!当然!
Mike: Oh, wow, sure!
劳拉∶这样写,给劳拉,
Laura-Lynn: Sign it, to Laura, the sexiest blonde I know,
我认识的最最性感的金发碧眼女郎,你的顺从的仆人,迈克尔西维尔.
your obedient servant, Michael Seaver.
麦琪∶好了,我去拿柠檬汁,孩子们,你们自己随便坐.
Maggie: OK, I'll get the lemonade; you kids pick your seats.
劳拉林∶谢谢.
Laura-Lynn: Thanks.
本∶你想看看迈克长大的房间吗?
Ben: So, would you like to see the room where Mike grew up?
劳拉∶哦!好的.
Laura-Lynn: Oh, that'd be lovely
本∶这衬衫也曾经是迈克的.
Ben: This shirt used to be Mike's.
劳拉林∶哇!
Laura-Lynn: Wow!
本∶裤子也是!
Ben: And the pants!
开萝尔∶迈克,你说了你的炸弹消息吗?
Carol: So, Mike have you dropped your bomb yet?
臭虫:不,那是我.对不起.
Stinky: No, that was me.I'm sorry.
迈克∶听着,开萝尔,你要再保持一个小时的沉默,可以吗?
Mike: Listen, Carol, I need one more hour of silence.Can you do that?
杰森∶大家坐紧一点.
Jason: OK, everybody sitting close together.
我要把每个人都拍进去.
I wanna get everybody in this shot.
迈克∶爸爸!你要录下节目,和看节目的我们?
Mike: Dad!You're taping the show, and you're taping us watching it?
杰森∶是的.
Jason: Yes I am.
迈克:好的,妈妈,
Mike: OK, Mom, Dad,
爸爸,演出之后我会宣布一下.
after the show I have a little announcement I'd like to make.
开萝尔∶你必须确保有足够多的带子.
Carol: And you'll want to make sure you save plenty of tape for that.
(在电视上看纽约风暴)
(Watching New York Heat on TV)
摩尔根奇斯∶(电视)我说过你正在犯一生当中最大的错误.你的电话不是时候,
Morgan Chase:(TV)I'm telling you you're making the biggest mistake of
我洗完澡后,再打给你,
your life.You caught me at a bad time chief,
行不?他在那里,
can I call you back after I finish showering?There he is!
他想跑,举起手来!
He's about to make his move.Alright, get your hands up!
迈克∶到了,到了!
Mike: This is it!This is it!
演员∶布考斯基被打中了!
Actor:(TV) Bukowski's been hit!
摩尔根奇斯∶布考斯基对不起;那子弹是要来打我的,挺住,
Morgan Chase: Bukowski!I'm sorry, that bullet was meant for me!
救护车马上来了.
Hang on, there's an ambulance on the way.
迈克∶他们把我的台词剪掉了!
Mike: They cut my lines!
麦琪∶你太棒了!我去拿蛋糕!
Maggie: You were wonderful!I'll get the cake!
迈克∶别提蛋糕了!你们还不明白吗?我,我,我的角色结束在剪辑工作室里了.
Mike: Forget the cake!Don't you guys understand?My...my...my part ended up on the cutting room floor!
杰森∶不要这样对自己.你刚才上了国家电视台!
Jason: Well, don't be so hard on yourself.You were just on National TV!
迈克∶但是,爸爸,你还不懂吗?我的台词被剪掉了!
Mike: But Dad, don't you get it, my lines were cut!
臭虫∶我以为你会有台词.
Stinky: I thought you were gonna talk in this show.
迈克∶我有的.
Mike: So did I.
麦琪∶哦!宝贝,当你中枪的时候,你倒下去的姿势很棒.
Maggie: Oh, but honey when you got shot, you did a wonderful fall.
迈克∶妈妈,那是替身演员!
Mike: Mom, that was a stunt man!
杰森∶咳嗽,咳嗽!咳嗽是你的!
Jason: The cough, the cough!It was a heck of a cough!
迈克∶爸爸,那咳嗽也不是我的.
Mike: Dad, it wasn't even my cough; they dubbed it!
是他们合成的.他说hahaha,我说huhuhu.
I mean, he went, hahaha, and I went huhuhu.
劳拉林∶我怎么会让你那样摸我呢!我感觉脏死了.
Laura-Lynn: And I let you grope me for that!I feel so dirty.
麦琪∶哦!信用.
Maggie: Oh, oh the credits.
杰森∶别这样,迈克!
Jason: Yeah, come on Mike!Let's get this in perspective here.
让我们看看演职员表,看看你完成了哪部分.
Let's look at what you have accomplished.
迈克∶咳嗽男孩!!迈克尔西维尔!!
Mike: Coughing Boy!!Michael Weaver!!
斯提克:这个夜晚真好.晚安,迈克,开萝尔,西维尔博士和夫人.
Stinky: Well, I had a lovely evening.Night Mike, Carol, doctor and Mrs.Weaver.
麦琪∶宝贝儿,别难过.这是你的第一份工作,你做的很好.
Maggie: Oh, honey, don't be upset.It was your first job, you did OK.
杰森∶对,迈克,他们选中你!
Jason: Yeah Mike, come on!They picked you!They paid you!
他们支付报酬给你!他们说你做的很好.就当做是一次学习的经历.
They said you did a good job.Think of it as a learning experience.
开萝尔∶像学校一样.
Carol: Sort of like school.
杰森:轻松一点的话题,迈克,你的重大宣布是什么?
Jason: Well, on a happier note...errm...Mike, what's the big announcement?
迈克∶宣告?……
Mike: Announcement?Well err...
开萝尔∶让我来说,迈克.
Carol: I'll tell them, Mike.
迈克∶……别说.
Mike: Err...No you won't.
开萝尔∶我要说.
Carol: Yes I will.
迈克∶不要,开萝尔.
Mike: No, Carol.
开萝尔∶你们不必担心迈克会当真,
Carol: Well, it's just that,
因此而退学;因为迈克知道他还有很多东西需要学,是吗,
you two shouldn't worry this'll go to Mike's head and make him drop out
迈克?
of school; because Mike knows he has a lot to learn, right Mike?
杰森∶对!
Mike: Err...Yeah!
麦琪∶迈克,是个成熟的看法.
Maggie: Mike, that's a very mature point of view.
杰森∶我一点也不怀疑你的能力.我们吃蛋糕吧.
Jason: I never doubted you for a minute.Let's eat that cake.
迈克∶开萝尔,你葫芦里到底卖的什么药?你替我说谎.
Mike: Alright, so what's going on here Carol?You covered for me.
开萝尔∶我承认,我并不是那么讨厌你.
Carol: OK, I'll admit it, I'm not totally grossed out to be related to you.
迈克∶不要对我假惺惺了.
Mike: Oh, come on, don't go getting all mushy on me.
开萝尔∶在我说你上电视前,我就会对你有一种不同的感觉,
Carol: It's just that when I say you on TV before,
那是自豪.
I felt something about you that I've never felt before...it's pride.
迈克∶开萝尔,你真的为我自豪?
Mike: Carol, you're....err...proud of me?
开萝尔∶是呀,谁会想到呢?
Carol: Yeah.Who knew?
迈克∶这么说来,你真的曾经在你朋友面前为我吹嘘过?
Mike: So you really were bragging to all your friends about me?
开萝尔∶吹嘘这个词太夸张了.
Carol: Bragging is such a strong word.
迈克∶那你说的你会站在我这边,支持我,
Mike: So you really meant it when you talked about being on my side and
爱我,也都是真的啦?
supporting me and loving me?
开萝尔:是.
Carol: Yeah.
开萝尔和迈克∶呵呵,不要告诉别人!
麦琪和杰森∶哇哇哇哇!
Carol and Mike: Don't tell anyone about this. Maggie and Jason: Wa wa wa wa wa wa wa wa